[
  {
    "title": "Spanish Cards",
    "setId": "4b9cfd4e-9cb7-4d10-b19d-52bb48a857f8",
    "description": "Spanish Vocab for my upcoming final",
    "reminderTime": "2024-09-27T00:00:00.000Z", 
    "numCards": 4,
    "cards": [
      {
        "cardId": "0",
        "question": "How do you say \"programming\" in Spanish?",
        "answer": "programación",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "1",
        "question": "How do you say \"dog\" Spanish?",
        "answer": "perro/perra",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "2",
        "question": "How do you say \"I go\" Spanish?",
        "answer": "voy",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "3",
        "question": "How do you say \"You need?\" Spanish?",
        "answer": "necesitas",
        "confidence": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Math Cards",
    "setId": "a69d7a63-9bc2-40ae-8e9a-56d7d21fa0b7",
    "description": "Math definitions for my discrete math final",
    "reminderTime": "2024-10-09T00:00:00.000Z", 
    "numCards": 3,
    "cards": [
      {
        "cardId": "0",
        "question": "Prime number?",
        "answer": "Only divisible by 1 and itself.",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "1",
        "question": "Pythagorean Theorem?",
        "answer": "a² + b² = c²",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "2",
        "question": "Set definition?",
        "answer": "A collection of distinct elements.",
        "confidence": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Physics Cards",
    "setId": "318f3cbb-2d9c-47d2-84e1-87461f73c57c",
    "description": "Physics formulas for my final",
    "reminderTime": "2024-10-27T00:00:00.000Z", 
    "numCards": 5,
    "cards": [
      {
        "cardId": "0",
        "question": "Newton's 2nd Law?",
        "answer": "F = ma",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "1",
        "question": "Kinetic energy?",
        "answer": "KE = 1/2 mv²",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "2",
        "question": "Gravitational PE?",
        "answer": "PE = mgh",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "3",
        "question": "Speed of light?",
        "answer": "3.00 × 10^8 m/s",
        "confidence": 0
      },
      {
        "cardId": "4",
        "question": "Ohm's Law?",
        "answer": "V = IR",
        "confidence": 0
      }
    ]
  }
]
